<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SageTVPlugin>
  <Name>Phoenix Core Services</Name>
  <Identifier>phoenix-core</Identifier>
  <Description>
Phoenix Core Services provides the following services
* automatic metadata and fanart fetching from external sources such as IMDb, TMDb, and TVDb.
* dynamic menus
* custom views
* user profiles
</Description>
  <Author>stuckless,meinmaui,bialio</Author>
  <CreationDate>2010.06.05</CreationDate>
  <ModificationDate>@@last-modified@@</ModificationDate>
  <ResourcePath>phoenix-core</ResourcePath>
  <Version>@@version@@</Version>

  <Webpage><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/showthread.php?t=36044]]></Webpage>

  <Dependency>
    <Plugin>phoenix-api</Plugin>
    <MinVersion>@@version@@</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <Dependency>
    <Plugin>commons-net</Plugin>
    <MinVersion>1.4.1</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <Dependency>
    <Plugin>htmlparser</Plugin>
    <MinVersion>1.6</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <Dependency>
    <Plugin>lucene-core</Plugin>
    <MinVersion>3.0.1</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>
  
  <PluginType>Standard</PluginType>

  <Package>
    <PackageType>System</PackageType>
    <Location>http://sagephoenix.googlecode.com/files/phoenix-core-@@version@@.zip</Location>
    <MD5>@@system-checksum@@</MD5>
  </Package>
  
  <ImplementationClass>sagex.phoenix.plugin.PhoenixPlugin</ImplementationClass>
  <ReleaseNotes>
2.5.5
* Weather updates by Jusjoken

2.5.4
* P2 Updates
* Added Nest themostat APIs

2.5.3
* Reverted to TMDB for Movie Metadata

2.5.1
* Fixes a minor issue preventing P2 from loading on Full Clients

2.5.0
* Restored IMDB support using Nielm's IMDB library
* Added Quotes and Trivia
* Replaced TheMovieDB with V3 Api (Should reduce the chances of getting Russian Fanart)
* Code changes to support Phoenix UI V2
* Adjusted Sage Recording metadata save/update so that if Preserve metadata is enabled, then blank fields are still updated

2.3.62
* Removed IMDB support (metadata provider is broken, and requires too much time to keep fixing it)
* Misc Phoenix Remote API updates required for the Phoenix Android App

2.3.61
* VFS: Fixed error whereby options were not be picked up the filters in a filter group
* VFS: Added better VFS organization and caching which allows for updating system level filters and sources
* Streaming: Added Phoenix Media Streamer for use with Phoenix Android App

2.3.60
* Fixed IMDb detail scraper

2.3.58
* fixed broken imdb searches
* misc tweaks from jusjoken for Gemstone
  
2.3.55
* More Weather fixes from Jusjoken 
 
2.3.54
* WeatherUnderground fixes

2.3.53
* UFT-8 fixes (ie, ensuring UTF-8 support)
* Fixed bugs in Set/Get default fanart -- imported jusjokens' fix for Season fanart
* Weather Underground support added by jusjoken 
 
2.3.52
* Added new Filters from jusjoken
* Updated phoenix rest apis

2.3.51
* Updated phoenix rest apis

2.3.50
* Added updated weather apis (with help from jusjoken)
* Updated phoenix rest apis
* Added upnp client/server support (just libraries and basic vfs browsing)

2.3.46
* Fixed Export Thumbnail issue (was creating 16x16 black images)
* Prevent the loading of invalid Skins
* Added Weather API
* Added IsType(HOME_VIDEO) 
* Added Gzip decompression for TVDB xml files 

2.3.44
* Fixed NullPointerExceptions that were showing up in the sagetv_0.txt
* Removed System.out messages that were showing up in the sagetv_0.txt
* Will automatically download x-vfs.xml if it is missing (ie, Phoenix UI is not installed)
* Fixed GetFanartEpisode (was always returning first image)
* Added option to disable local fanart
* Fixed GetFanartAlbum (was always returning first image)
* Added better recovery code for failed TVDB searches (ie, should retry)
* Fixed menu sort issue
* Moved BMT views to BMT plugin

2.3.43
* Minor change adding support for album.jpg

2.3.42
* Minor changes to support Phoenix UI build 405
* Removed vfs.xml. x-vfs.xml is provided in PhoenixUI or users can manually download x-vfs.xml

2.3.41
* Changed the default xml parsing to not abort on xml errors.  This should allow the Phoenix system to start up even where there are invalid xml elements, etc. 
* Fixed bug in music fanart download that results in excessive downloads from the HTBackdrops server
* Added REST apis for Phoenix

2.3.40
* Music Fanart download support (for Artist only)
* Music Fanart support (Album and Artist)
* Fixed bug in IMDB provider
* Group by Substring of Title
* Added Partially Watched and Recently Watched filters
* Fixed Fanart bug when MediaTitle is null
* Misc Fanart tweaks to try and make better decisions when some items are missing MediaTitle/MediaType
  </ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>
